Marta: This happened two years ago.
I’m Spanish, but I was in Ireland at the time because I had a job in Dublin.
Some friends of mine who lived in Lyon, in France, invited me to come and stay,
so I decided to have a short holiday, a long weekend, from Friday to Tuesday.
I looked for cheap flights, but I couldn’t find any direct ones.
The only thing I could find was Ryanair from Dublin to Brussels,
and then Air France from Brussels to Lyon.
Anyway, the flight to Brussels was fine,
and when I arrived, I went to the gate for my next flight to Lyon,
but, then when I needed to show my boarding pass and my ID, I couldn’t find my ID card.
I looked everywhere – in my bag, in my case – but it wasn’t there.
The people at the gate were very nice and they made some phone calls,
but nobody could find it.
So they told me to wait in a small room and I sat there for more than an hour,
and my flight to Lyon left without me.
It was awful – I cried – I was so stressed and unhappy.
In the end, a policeman came and he said that I couldn’t go to France
because I didn’t have any ID –
the only place I could go was to Spain to get a new ID card!
I waited another five or six hours for the flight to Madrid, feeling very depressed.
So I never had my holiday!
I spent the weekend in Madrid getting my new ID card!